<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Syringes &#8211; Cosmetic  Trading B.V.</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product-category/syringes/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/M9S-large_favicon-100x100.png</url>
	<title>Syringes &#8211; Cosmetic  Trading B.V.</title>
	<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Disposable Luer Lock Syringe</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-luer-lock-syringe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6652/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">1,000,000pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

*Disposable syringes
*Disposable infusion sets
*transfusion sets
*Scalp vein set
Our company was certified by CFDA, CE, ISO13485 and ISO9001, approved by GMP .

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Disposable Syringe Series</p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Types: Two-parts or three-parts, Luer slip or luer lock</li>
<li>Specification:1ml,3ml, 5ml, 10ml, 20ml, 30ml, 50ml, 60ml, 100ml</li>
<li>Needle size: 16G to 30G</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing: PE package, paper-plastic package, Laminated film with dialyzing paper package, Blister package</li>
<li>OEM can be arranged</li>
</ul>
<p><img title="disposable syringe" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908061034271293.JPG" alt="disposable syringe" /><img title="syringe luer lock" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908061034410390.JPG" alt="syringe luer lock" /></p>
<p>The Disposable syringe is specially designed for human subcutaneous, flesh, muscle, vein and other injections. Its main materials, structure and performance are as follows:</p>
<p>1. Materials and structures</p>
<p>The product consists of a jacket (polypropylene), a core rod (polypropylene), a rubber piston (natural rubber), and an injection needle.</p>
<p>2. Main technical parameters and requirements</p>
<p>(1) Body tightness 300kpa and 3.0N force core rod 30S does not leak, 60±5S under 88kpa negative pressure does not leak, piston core rod does not separate;</p>
<p>(2) Good sliding performance.</p>
<p>Disposable syringe treatment method</p>
<p>Disposable syringes are medical wastes and cannot be disposed of as freely as normal garbage. They are placed in trash cans for recycling. Such medical wastes are generally disposed of in a centralized and harmless manner, including incineration, destructive disinfection, and deep burial after incineration. When using a safety box for incineration, the temperature should be above 800 °C to reduce air pollution; if there is no safety box, a lower incinerator with a temperature (300 ° C ~ 400 ° C) can also be used. In areas where there are no destroyers and incinerators, the method of deep burying after incineration can be used.</p>
<p>Here, we must remind everyone that disposable syringes should not be recycled at will. Some disposable medicines will have some residual medicines that are not cleaned, so be sure to pay attention to them. You can&#8217;t ignore them. not allowed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Luer Slip Injection Syringe</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-luer-slip-injection-syringe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6654/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">500,000 pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

1, Effective communication and prompt response.
2, High quality products support you to win your market.
3, Commit to new and innovative technology to meet latest market demand.
4, Develop new and unique products with you.
5, Any suggestions for our products and price, etc. are welcomed

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Disposable Syringe Series</strong></p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Types: Two-parts or three-parts, Luer slip or luer lock</li>
<li>Specification:1ml,3ml, 5ml, 10ml, 20ml, 30ml, 50ml, 60ml, 100ml</li>
<li>Needle size: 16G to 30G</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing: PE package, paper-plastic package, Laminated film with dialyzing paper package, Blister package</li>
<li>OEM can be arranged</li>
</ul>
<p><img title="injection syringe" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908061034271293.JPG" alt="injection syringe" /><img title="syringe luer slip" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908061034410390.JPG" alt="syringe luer slip" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disposable syringe handling regulations</p>
<p>Disposable syringes cannot be discarded at will after use. General hospitals have certain regulations for the use of syringes. The specific systems generally include the following points.</p>
<p>1. The inoculation unit should have a person responsible for the disinfection and destruction of disposable syringes.</p>
<p>2. Establish a disposable syringe to transfer or purchase, use, destroy records, the records should be fully recorded, and the accounts are consistent.</p>
<p>3. Vaccination should use a disposable syringe.</p>
<p>4, the use of disposable syringes for vaccination, must strictly implement the &#8220;one person, one needle, one tube, one use and one destruction&#8221; system.</p>
<p>5. When using the disposable syringe, the staff of the primary inoculation unit should check whether the syringe packaging is intact and the product has been damaged or has expired within the validity period.</p>
<p>6. When the inoculation is completed, the disposable syringe should be placed in a puncture-proof safety collection container (safety box) made of solid material and handed in before the next inoculation. Do not reuse disposable syringes.</p>
<p>7. After use, the disposable syringe can be destroyed by the destroyer, or the needle and the syringe can be separated by manual destruction. The needle can be directly placed into the stab-resistant container or bent with a pliers 90 degrees or more, and the syringe is clamped with pliers. The nipple is immersed for more than 60 minutes with a disinfectant containing 1000 mg/L of available chlorine.</p>
<p>Finally, a unified treatment for destruction, incineration or burial is used to ensure the one-time use of the syringe.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable IV Infusion Set</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-iv-infusion-set/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6656/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Transparent &#38; flexible drip chamber
15 micron fluid filter in drip chamber
Soft and kink resistant PVC tubing ensures uniform flow rate
Smooth roller clamp facilitates easy, safe control and adjustment of fluid rates
Standard tube length : 150 cms
Tube dia : I Ø 3.0 mm, O Ø 4.1 mm]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Disposable infusion set</strong></p>
<ol class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Components: vented spikes / non vented spikes, drip chambers, roller clamps, Y-connectors, Luer slip/lock connectors, PVC tube, air inlet filters, needle</li>
<li>Raw material: PVC, ABS or PP</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO9001, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing； PE or Blister pouch, Inner box, Export carton. OEM can be arranged</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="Disposable infusion set" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201909091533586160.jpg" alt="Disposable infusion set" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The main structure of disposable intravenous infusion set:</p>
<p>The secondary intravenous infusion set is mainly composed of a medicine inlet cap, a medicine inlet joint, a catheter, a flow stop clip, a liquid medicine filter, a medicine outlet joint, and a medicine outlet guard cap. The catheter is mainly made of soft polyvinyl chloride (PVC) material for blood transfusion (liquid) appliance, medicine feeding cap, medicine inlet joint, flow stop clamp, liquid medicine filter, medicine outlet joint, medicine outlet cap It is mainly made of acrylonitrile-styrene-butadiene copolymer (ABS) material.</p>
<p>Scope of application:</p>
<p>Disposable intravenous infusion set performance and use:</p>
<p>The disposable intravenous infusion set can be equipped with a liquid medicine filter, which is mainly used for infusion devices (infusion sets, infusion pumps, syringes, micro-injection pumps), and is used when the infusion liquid medicine needs to be lengthened.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Oral Medication Syringe With Adaptor</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-oral-medication-syringe-with-adaptor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6658/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">1,000,000pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

1. Sufficiently transparent barrel allows easy measurement of the volume contained in the syringe and detection of air bubble.
2. Graduated scale on the barrel is easy to read.
3. The plunger fits the inside of barrel very well to allow for free and smooth movement.
4. KDL needle has more reasonable needle tip edge angle ,the maximum to reduce the puncture pain.
5. Non-toxic, non-pyrogenic and EO sterilized
6. SIize:1ml,2ml,3ml,5ml,10ml,20ml,30ml,50ml,60ml
7. With needle or without needle. The type of needle according to the customer request. the sizes 18G to 26G are available.
8. CE &#38; ISO certificate

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>oral syringe</strong></p>
<p><img title="oral medication syringe" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908061016320137.jpg" alt="oral medication syringe" /></p>
<p>Size: 1ml, 2/3ml, 5ml, 10ml, 20ml</p>
<p>With adaptor</p>
<p>Package:1pc/bag</p>
<p>1. Sufficiently transparent barrel allows easy measurement of the volume contained in the syringe and detection of air bubble.</p>
<p>2. Graduated scale on the barrel is easy to read.</p>
<p>3. The plunger fits the inside of barrel very well to allow for free and smooth movement.</p>
<p>4. KDL needle has more reasonable needle tip edge angle ,the maximum to reduce the puncture pain.</p>
<p>5. Non-toxic, non-pyrogenic and EO sterilized</p>
<p>6. SIize:1ml,2ml,3ml,5ml,10ml,20ml,30ml,50ml,60ml</p>
<p>7. With needle or without needle. The type of needle according to the customer request. the sizes 18G to 26G are available.</p>
<p>8. CE &amp; ISO certificate</p>
<p>Product features</p>
<p>Some syringes have a screw port design, and the double-threaded needle is used for better post-destruction treatment. The existing self-destructing syringe is used to retract the needle after use, to catch the core rod or to automatically break the core rod. Can not be used again with polypropylene material, good biocompatibility, high transparency, clear and accurate tick mark, good sliding performance, easy to use, self-destructing structure, easy to use after single use Harmful treatment</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Blood Transfusion Set</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-blood-transfusion-set/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6660/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">500,000 pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

FEATURES ::
Available in Single-drip/Double-drip chamber variants.
soft kink resistance and translucent tubing is prepared from medical treated PVC material.
Approx 200 micron blood filter and 18 G hypodermic needle
Strong and sharp spike for easy insertion in Blood container.
Roller clamp able to control the flow of the blood infusion also do not kink on the tube.
Drip chamber with filter mesh to keep out blood clots from entering the patient''s circulation.

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Disposable blood transfusion set</strong></p>
<ol class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Material: polypropylene</li>
<li>Application: used for human blood transfusion</li>
<li>Steel needle spike and plastic spike available</li>
<li>Series available: BT-1, BT-3, BT-4, BT-5, BT-6</li>
<li>Luer slip adapter with hypodermic needle</li>
<li>Sterilization: ethylene-gas-sterilization</li>
<li>Expiration date: 3 years from the date of manufacture</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO9001, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing: PE package or blister package. OEM can be arranged</li>
</ol>
<p><img title="Blood transfusion set" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201909091545115684.jpg" alt="Blood transfusion set" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disposable blood transfusion set device with medical grade polyvinyl chloride as the main raw material with protective sleeve, puncture device, blood and blood product filter net, dropper, drip bucket, drip bucket outlet hose, flow regulator, plug-in conical joint, Medical device consisting of accessories such as liquid injection parts. It can be used to save patients with major bleeding or blood transfusion during surgery. After use, it can be discarded to avoid cross-infection and ensure safe use.</p>
<p>product advantages:</p>
<p>The filter membrane of the precision filter is made of polyethersulfone. The filtration rate is high, reaching more than 99%; the infusion speed is fast, there is no clogging phenomenon; the biocompatibility is good, there is no drug adsorption; no foreign matter falls off in the downstream, and no secondary pollution is caused;the filter design is exquisite, exhaust fast. No bubbles remain; no leakage;</p>
<p>The infusion pipeline adopts high-quality and high-elastic material, the pipe wall is smooth, it is not easy to adhere to air bubbles, the material is soft and not easy to be discounted, and it can also meet the infusion requirements well in winter;the use of imported intravenous infusion needle, sharp needle tip, good rigidity.</p>
<p>Product specifications:</p>
<p>In order to meet different clinical needs, a variety of filter pore filter membranes were designed, which are 5.0um, 3.0um, 2.0um, 1.2um0.2um, which are the most complete domestic specifications, and each type has domestic filter. And imported filters are available. Insert bottle needle, double steel needle, new patented plastic steel insert needle, integrated curved plastic insert needle.</p>
<p>The scope of use of each regulation:</p>
<p>Applicable people: children, elderly patients, chemotherapy patients, postoperative patients, critically ill patients, cardiovascular patients, patients who need long-term infusion.</p>
<p>Applicable drugs: traditional Chinese medicine, antibiotics, nutrient solution, potassium chloride, fructose, mannitol, fat emulsion, chemotherapy drugs, lansalazole for injection, etc.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Atraumatic Suture</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-atraumatic-suture/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6663/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">500,000 pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

About the Surgical Sture:
*A surgical suture is the material used to hold a wound or cut together until it heals.
*Suturing is the act of stitching or sewing the wound using suture materials such as thread or a surgical staple.
*The area that requires a suture may be the result of injuries or surgery, and the style of suture used depends on where in the body the surgical suture is needed.

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Disposable surgical atraumatic suture series</strong></p>
<ol class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>types: polyester, polypropylene, stainless steel, polyamide, plain catgut, silk, nylon, chromic catgut, polyglycolic acid, polyglactine swift</li>
<li>Point type of needle: taper point needle, blunt taper point needle, tapercut needle,cutting needle, reverse cutting needle, micro-point spatula needle</li>
<li>Needle diameter range: 0.2-0.4mm, 0.5-0.7mm, 0.8-1.0mm, 1.1-1.3mm</li>
<li>Specification: 0,2-0,3-0,4-0,5-0,6-0,7-0,8-0,9-0,10-0,11-0,12-0 etc</li>
<li>Suture types: absorbableor non-absorbable</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO9001, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing: blister package. OEM can be arranged</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Absorbable Suture</strong></p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Chromic catgut</li>
<li>Plain catgut</li>
<li>Poliglecaprone</li>
<li>Polydioxanone</li>
<li>Polyglactin 910</li>
<li>Polyglycolic acid</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Non-absorbable Suture<br />
</strong></p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Nylon monofilament</li>
<li>ophthalmatic sutures</li>
<li>Polyester braided</li>
<li>Polypropylene monofilament</li>
<li>Silk braided<strong><br />
</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><img title="Disposable atraumatic suture" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201909091608031503.jpg" alt="Disposable atraumatic suture" /></p>
<p>Disposable Atraumatic Suture refers to a special line used for ligation, hemostasis, and tissue suture during surgery or trauma treatment. Generally, it can be divided into two categories: absorbable lines and non-absorbable lines.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disposable atraumatic suture characteristics</p>
<p>1. Versatility, suture material is suitable for any operation. 2. Non-electrolytic, no surface tension, no allergic and no carcinogenicity. 3. Sterility, mild tissue response, is not conducive to bacterial growth. 4. Easy to operate, firm and with proper tensile strength.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Suture selection principle</p>
<p>1. Absorbable sutures are used to heal faster tissues, especially in areas where foreign bodies should not be left, such as the gastrointestinal tract, bile duct, urinary tract, and myometrium.</p>
<p>2. Non-absorbable sutures are used to heal slow tissues such as cartilage, ligaments, tendons, bronchi, esophagus, and grafts that require long-term fixation.</p>
<p>3. Single-fiber sutures are used in vascular surgery and orthopedics.</p>
<p>4. For some special patients, such as the elderly, diabetic patients, obesity patients, malnourished patients, debilitated patients, etc., the suture should be paid attention to the impact of suture on the healing rate and process of postoperative wounds. A suture with the same toughness and minimal tissue response.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable IV Cannula Needles</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-iv-cannula-needles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6665/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">1,000,000pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

1. E.O. Gas Sterilized,Piercing Needles Individually Packaged,Needles Come With Sleeve To Protect The Tip
2. Teri-Beveled Medical Grade Single Use Professional Piercing Needles
3. Piercing Needles are Extremely well-manufactured, high-quality,Stylish and lightweight,easy to take.
4. Professional Packaging to protect your items

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IV Cannula needle</p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>With wing IV cannula needle</li>
</ul>
<p><img title="Disposable IV cannula needles" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908271444540473.jpg" alt="Disposable IV cannula needles" /></p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>With-injection-port IV Cannula</li>
</ul>
<p><img title="IV Catheter Needles Kit Piercing for IV Start Kits" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908271445328430.jpg" alt="IV Catheter Needles Kit Piercing for IV Start Kits" /></p>
<ul class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Pen-like IV Cannula</li>
</ul>
<p><img title="Safety FEP Straight IV Catheter" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908271445546931.jpg" alt="Safety FEP Straight IV Catheter" /></p>
<p>The products should be used with disposable venous infusion setneedle, and usually apply togravity transfusion.</p>
<p>The disposable IV infusion set needle consist of protective cover, needle tube, needle handle, flexible tube, needle seat.</p>
<p>Product Application: Used together with disposable draw blood needle, for human body&#8217;s IV bloodsample collecting in clinical examination.</p>
<p><strong>How to practice a good intravenous needle technique</strong></p>
<p>If you want to practice a good venous needle technique, you must first adjust your mentality. You have to know that in an impatient situation, you can&#8217;t do this at all, and your patients are waiting for you to infuse him. After years of clinical practice, the more urgent you can&#8217;t get on. of. Therefore, when performing venipuncture, you must have a calm mentality.</p>
<p>In order to practice a good venous needle technique, it is also necessary to grasp the characteristics of the venous blood vessels. For example, the characteristics of venous blood vessels in obese people, the characteristics of venous blood vessels of bones (that is, the kind of sputum, which is completely skinny), where the blood vessels are slippery, not fixed enough, these must know, also There are spare blood vessels in the case of anxious conditions, such as blood vessels at the joints of the fingers, especially at the thumb.</p>
<p>If you want to practice a good venous needle technique, you need to pick the right blood vessels. When performing a venipuncture operation, select those blood vessels that are straight, thick, and elastic, avoiding the switch joints, and avoiding the venous valve. Sometimes you don&#8217;t get it, but you don&#8217;t pick it up.</p>
<p>If you want to practice the venous needle technique, you need to use the venipuncture operation. After the skin is disinfected, your hands should be well-fitted. The left hand should tighten the skin at the vein, and then the right hand can Hold the scalp needle for this operation. The purpose of tightening the skin is to fix the blood vessels, so that you can puncture.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Insulin Syringe</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-insulin-syringe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6667/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">1000000pcs per month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

Usage：
1.For insulin injection;.
2 With fixed needle;
3 Material: medical-grade PP or PVC;
4 Transparent barrel and plunger;
5 Latex or latex free rubber piston.
Package :100 syringes in pack

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Product name: disposable insulin syringe</p>
<p>Description:</p>
<ol class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>specification: 1ml, 0.5ml</li>
<li>Type: U-100,U-40</li>
<li>Hypodermic needle: 30G, 29G</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO9001, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing: PE or Blister Poich, Inner Box, Export Carton. OEM can be arranged</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Product introduction</p>
<p>1, the jacket is transparent, easy to observe the liquid surface and bubbles</p>
<p>2. The 6:100 conical joint designed according to the national standard can be used with any product with standard 6:100 conical joint.</p>
<p>3, the product is well sealed, does not leak</p>
<p>4, sterile, pyrogen free</p>
<p>5, the scale ink adhesion is strong, does not fall off</p>
<p>6, the fine needle tip configuration, to achieve painless injection, reduce user fear</p>
<p>7, humanization considerations, the color of the cap is different from the insulin intensity (40U/100U) to prevent the use of the wrong concentration</p>
<p>8, one-piece structure, the amount of liquid residue is very small, to ensure the accuracy of drug delivery</p>
<p>Product important features:</p>
<p>The needle tube is ultra-fine, sharp, and particularly easy to penetrate;</p>
<p>No dead space syringes avoid the waste of insulin;</p>
<p>The bold scale is easier to read.</p>
<p>Precautions for use</p>
<p>1. Use a new needle for each injection.</p>
<p>2. With a needle storage companion pen may cause insulin leakage and bubble formation in the core.</p>
<p>3. Discharge air every time.</p>
<p>4. When exhausting, be sure to let the insulin pen drop out. This is done to ensure that there are no air bubbles in the pen. Ensure that the dose is sufficient.</p>
<p>5. When the needle of the accompaniment pen penetrates into the skin, press the injection button to maintain the pressure and press it firmly on the button while slowly counting to 5. Then, it is confirmed that the injection is completed when the 0 dose mark is at the center of the window.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Spinal Needles</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-spinal-needles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6669/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">1,000,000pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

Single-use Spinal Needle
1. For epidural nerve block and subarachnoid anaesthesia on patient in clinical surgery. The sharp casing enhanced smoothing over inter-organnizational, lower puncture resistance, and the depth marking on the casing make the positioning more accurate.
2. State of the art technology is used to smooth and perfect the eliptial point to ensure easy entry into body tissues, needle sizes are colour coded, thin wall needle has a larger lumen space, due to maximumlume a thinner needle can be used for an application

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>spinal needle</strong></p>
<p><img title="Disposable Spinal needles" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201908271447297344.jpg" alt="Disposable Spinal needles" /></p>
<p data-spm-anchor-id="a2700.details.pronpeci14.i0.1acd3ba8LlbRP0">Two type;Quincke type and pencil type<br />
Used in subarachnoid puncture for spinal anesthesia<br />
The sharp casing enhanced smoothing over inter-organnizational, lower puncture resistance<br />
Transparent hub,easy to observe the cerebrospinal fluid discharge<br />
Hub with lock can keep the surface of needle bevel joint well<br />
Color coded hub by size for clear recognition<br />
Size:18G-27G Length:50-110mm<br />
Packing: individual blister package<br />
Steriled by Eo gas, non-toxic, non-pyrogenic, single use only</p>
<p>Customer special needle size per specification</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Product Usage</strong></p>
<p>This product is a sterile puncture needle, which can be used for human puncture and spinal anesthesia. The basic function is aspiration and injection. It can be used for diagnosis and treatment.</p>
<p><strong>Product advantages</strong></p>
<p>The disposable spine tip is specially treated specially, the needle is smooth and the linearity is good; the inner wall of the needle cavity is treated with a special surface, which not only has good uniformity but also good surface slidability, and the liquid passage resistance is very small. The unique needle design makes it not cut tissue and nerve needle during puncture, but squeeze and separate needle. The puncture needle will naturally close under the elastic packing of the tissue, and the recovery speed is greater than other types of needles, greatly reducing Tissue damage.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disposable Transfusion Blood Bag</title>
		<link>https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/disposable-transfusion-blood-bag/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cosmetictradingbv.com/product/import-placeholder-for-6671/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<div class="product-attributes-item">
<ul>
 	<li><label>Brand </label><span class="info-deta">None</span></li>
 	<li><label>Product origin </label><span class="info-deta">Made in China</span></li>
 	<li><label>Delivery time </label><span class="info-deta">According to quantity</span></li>
 	<li><label>Supply capacity </label><span class="info-deta">500,000 pcs/month</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="product-overview">

Product name: Disposable blood bags (with anticoagulant) for blood transfusion
Specification
1. Configuration: single bag, double bag, triple blood bag, quadruple blood bag and transfer bag
2. Size:250ml, 350ml, 450ml,500ml
3. Anticoagulants: CPDA-1,CPDA+SAGM
6. Needle: 16 G sharp pointed needle that is siliconised with ultra-thin walled
7. Tube:provided with standard donor tubing with code number on the tube surface.
8.It adopts high grade medical PVC made in or . They're accessible with integrated donor tubing at regular intervals for easy cross matching, processing and identification.

</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Disposable blood bags</strong></p>
<ol class=" list-paddingleft-2">
<li>Anticoagulants: CPDA-1, SAGM</li>
<li>Type: single bag, double bag, triple bag and quadruple bag</li>
<li>Size: 100ml, 250ml, 350ml, 450ml, 500ml</li>
<li>Sterilized, non-toxic, pyrogen-free</li>
<li>Sanitary standard and quality in accordance with the CE, FDA, ISO9001, ISO13485 standards</li>
<li>Packing: every set with PE compounded vacuum bag, every three to five sets with aluminum foil compounded bag. OEM can be arranged</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="blood bag" src="https://img.waimaoniu.net/1453/1453-201909091616092090.jpg" alt="blood bag" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Quality Features：</strong></p>
<p>Designed for collection, storage, transfusion and transportation of human blood and its components.</p>
<p>Manufactured from high quality medical grade plasticized PVC compatible with blood having properties such as non-toxicity, transparency, flexibility, high tensile strength, heat and cold resistance.</p>
<p>Ultra-thin walled 16G Venipuncture needle is optimal for reducing donor pain</p>
<p>Excellent twist-off needle cover makes the needle non-reusable.</p>
<p>Highly flexible and kink-resistant blood collecting tube includes serial numbers for precise, easy identification</p>
<p>The breakaway valve is designed for quick and easy opening of the fluid paths between bags.</p>
<p>Safe and easy-to-open out-let port design provides protection from contamination.</p>
<p>High quality, peel-resistant label provides convenient recording</p>
<p>Dual packaging (Individual &amp; Aluminum) eliminates microbial contamination on the surface and maintains the content of anti.</p>
<p>Sterilized by steam in high pressure can assure products non-pyrogen and toxin-free.</p>
<p>Extrusion type and roll welding type blood bags can satisfy different costumers&#8217; requests.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
